[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
Kum.
I want to go public.
Is that a good idea, Anda?
Your family isn't okay with this, are they?
Anda.
Why did you come home so early?
You know what your dad is like lately.
Can you pretend you're hitting on me?
Okay.
I'll hit on you.
Sheesh...
Is my friend about to get into a relationship?
If that's the case, the rivalry between the two faculties is over.
Now they're two loving faculties.
I've got this for you.
I think you'll like it.
Where did you get this?
Hey, are those the freshmen?
Yeah. They probably just got back from camp.
- See you. - Let me talk to him.
That kid, what's his name?
It's Satang, a first-year Automotive Engineering student.
Hello, hello.
How are things? Was the camp fun?
It was.
But I almost got my face burned off. It was scorching hot.
I thought you'd be there, too.
Us, really? How would we even make it?
We already don't have time to work on our project.
Gosh. It's just a project. What's to worry about?
You're just that cool, you know?
Jinna.
I really like you.
What the hell? That came out of nowhere.
No. I mean, you're my idol.
In both sports and academics.
- You play soccer, too? - I do.
I played for my school.
- You sure you can handle it? - I'm up for any challenge.
God damn.
- Satang, right? - Yes. I'm Satang.
A girly name, right?
I wanted a different name, but she insisted on Thai currency names.
Why? You've got a cool name. Sounds like you'll make a fortune.
Tod, what kind of currency would I be?
"Euro?" Because I'm handsome.
Judging by your looks, I'd say "bottle caps"
because it sounds like "crap."
Damn you! You and your foul mouth.
My older brother is also named after a currency,
but it's obsolete now.
What currency is obsolete now?
His name is "Podduang."
He's a third-year student, just like you.
Podduang from the Sports and Health Science?
Right on the money.
You know him?
What, seriously? Podduang is interning at the soccer club.
- We know him. - Really?
Damn, you know him?
Of course. I know him well!
Podduang, why didn't you tell me?
You get to be in the same club as Jinna, and see him every day.
I would've joined too if I'd known.
The internship is necessary.
I'm not passionate about soccer.
No. You know how hot Jinna is, right?
Just watching him play soccer is a feast for the eyes.
He's great at both academics and sports.
He's simply perfect.
Dig in already, or it'll get cold.
Right, Podduang.
Do you know that all the pretty girls at university have a crush on Jinna?
I'm so jealous. He's my idol.
My friends in the same year also have a crush on him.
You have a chance to get close to Jinna, so dig around for me.
Find out why he's so perfect and good-looking.
Is he already taken?
Finish your food already.
You're talking too much!
[Jinna Ronnarak is calling]
Keep eating and don't stop.
What the hell? You just won't stop talking.
What? What are you waiting for?
- I know. - The food's getting cold!
Hello.
Why are you calling me?
Who are you hiding from? Why the whispering?
Don't ask.
Just tell me what's up.
Oh. You're afraid Satang would overhear you.
You know Satang, too?
Of course.
He introduced himself to me
as if he wanted to be my little brother.
Just ignore him. He's got a few screws loose.
Also, don't tell him about our deal, all right?
Why?
Are you embarrassed?
I'm not!
I just don't want him to find out.
I actually don't want anyone else to do the same.
I'm this good-looking, and you're not going to show me off?
I only want you to pretend to hit on me.
Don't get too attached.
I don't like pretending, though.
That's not what I meant. I only want you to pretend.
You're just that slow, aren't you?
How many times do I have to explain it to you?
Can you stay with me and keep explaining everything like this?
Right. I'm getting sleepy. I'm going to bed.
Oh, fine.
Why the "Oh"? You called just to mess with me.
I want to talk to you, all right?
That's it.
That's it? What?
That's what I call pretending to hit on me.
Podduang, I told you I don't like pretending.
Right, right. Fine.
I'll let you go to sleep, then.
Sweet dreams.
Sweet dreams, my ass?
[Characters, places, and incidents in this production]
[are entirely fictitious.]
[Viewer discretion is advised.]
[Rising Star Awards]
This feels like a dream.
I dreamed of standing here, receiving the "Rising Star Award,"
surrounded by people who applauded me and supported me.
I'd like to thank my agency for always taking care of me.
I'd also like to thank the crew, my manager,
and everyone who played a part in getting me to where I am right now.
More importantly, I'd like to thank all my fans,
both those who are here today and those watching at home.
I promise you that from now on, I'll keep improving myself every single day.
Your love really keeps me moving forward.
On top of that,
I'd like to thank my family for always being right by my side.
Finally, I'd like to thank my loved one
for always standing right beside me no matter what happens.
This award is for you all. Thank you!
[Love Anda, Team Anda]
- Anda! Anda! Anda! - Anda! Anda! Anda!
- Anda, can I take a picture with you? - Absolutely.
I'd truly like to thank all of you from the bottom of my heart.
[Andaman]
Ta-da!
- Whoa! - Congratulations, my rising star!
Thank you.
Here.
- Thank you very much. It's gorgeous. - What do you think? Are you tired?
I had to talk to so many people, Kum.
But you're happy, right?
Today, I got to meet my fans.
And when I got to thank them in person, I felt really happy.
That's good. I'm happy for you too.
By the way, did you have anything beforehand?
I had dessert at the ceremony.
When we get home, I'll order you something delicious, okay?
I can't wait to eat the world's largest pizza.
Sure thing. Hey, let me see the award!
- Wow. - "Anda."
[Faculty of Engineering]
Our rising star is here!
You've got that aura.
- Look. - I'm going blind from it.
Always with the teasing?
Congratulations. I told you you'd win the award either way.
Your name is all over the damn media this year.
Isn't it because of the backlash?
Hey, you're overthinking it.
Where there's love, there's hate. That's just how it goes.
At least more people love you than hate you.
What is certain is that we love you the most.
- I'm going to throw up. - How could you say that?
So you do know how to say nice things.
Of course.
The question is, where should we celebrate tonight?
- Not this again. - Oh, you prick.
- Enough already. - Watch it.
So where are we celebrating? Ask Kum to join us, too.
Well, a friend's friend's place, then.
I'll bring Kum there, too, so I don't have to worry about paparazzi.
You're so lucky to have a good boyfriend.
Well, of course. I'm already unlucky enough to have you.
What? This damn celebrity. You're getting on my nerves.
- I'll kick your ass. - Don't.
- Don't. - Don't you dare. Ever.
Jeez, not going to say hi?
We were talking the whole night.
Hey. Don't make it sound like that.
We were just on the phone.
That's what I meant.
How did you interpret it?
Where are you going after this?
To my room, obviously. Satang is waiting for me for dinner.
Oh, well. Never mind.
Tonight, I'm drinking with my friends.
Go on, then. Why are you telling me that?
Just letting you know in case I don't call you.
No need to wait for me, understand?
Who says I do?
Are you full of yourself?
You're talking nonsense.
You're wasting my time here.
Lost. You've lost it.
You like my friend that much, don't you?
That much, yeah.
All right, all right. Cheers to my rising star!
- All right, cheers. - Yeah.
You just love calling me by my award title?
It's the opposite of my state, so I'm drinking with you.
The series that got put on hold...
Gosh! It can stay that way.
Your ship partner's a freak. All he cares about is the trend.
That day, when he came to our faculty, he was lucky Jinna and I didn't beat him.
Try brushing it off.
Announcing like that means you respect your loved one,
your fans, and yourself.
It's true.
Winning the award already proves that the community accepts you.
In the end, no matter who you are, we're all human, Anda.
Right, right, right.
I'm trying to stop thinking about it.
But you know that, don't you?
Even though the whole world accepts me, my family...
Enough of that, Anda. Let's stop talking about serious stuff.
We're here to celebrate, aren't we?
You're right.
You guys, why are you all so serious?
Come on, a toast.
I won't let you off until you're hammered.
All right.
You're drunk. Take it easy already.
Jinna, why don't you find yourself a partner?
Just look at mine. He's so handsome and good.
Aren't you envious?
What the hell?
Are you showing off your partner now?
I'm not. I'm serious.
I'm so damn fortunate to have Kum as my boyfriend.
Is that so?
I'd be able to go on if I broke up with him?
Why do you ask that, Anda?
Well, I'm thinking about the worst-case scenario.
I'll never break up with you, no matter what.
You're so sweet.
You pass out every damn time you take a sip.
If it weren't for me, you'd probably be missing a kidney now.
Take care of me until old age, then.
- There, tell that to your boyfriend. - Jinna.
I'm going to go back to drinking now.
Thanks, Jinna. I'll take it from here.
He might throw up in the car, all right?
Come, Anda. Let's go home. Careful now.
There are steps. Come on.
Take a step.
Slowly.
[Stadium]
Careful. Take the ball.
Where are Tod and Art?
They're talking to a professor. They'll be here soon.
I have to leave a bit early, though.
Need to take care of something.
Go and rest up.
We're worried about you.
Podduang.
Do you need help?
It's okay, Anda. I'm used to it now.
I think...
I need to go now.
Tell Tod and Art for me, okay?
Right. Don't worry. Stay safe.
Bye.
Anda!
Get some proper rest if you're sleepy.
Don't sleep in the car.
Okay.
Why do you keep staring?
Well, do you know Jinna, right?
Of course, you've been talking about him daily.
No, not like that.
I mean, you know each other, don't you?
Well, of course we do. I'm an intern at the soccer club.
And, like, how well do you know each other?
Is it more than just friends?
You know what? Just get to the point, Satang.
No, well...
There's a rumor going around at the university
that Jinna is hitting on a Sports and Health Science student.
I just want to know who it is.
My friends in the faculty say that...
He's been hitting on you.
Right. Listen up.
Jinna and I are just...
[Jinna Ronnarak is calling]
I knew it!
You two are video calling each other.
Say it and make my night.
You really had to call at the perfect time.
If this is nothing important, I'll scold you like there's no tomorrow!
Just you wait!
Miss you.
Aren't you too invested?
This is nothing but a play. Don't forget that.
Why?
Why are we only pretending?
I told you I hate pretending.
Why? If I actually wanted to hit on you, that wouldn't be okay?
You're kidding me, right?
You think?
God! Why can't you just answer me directly?
Why do you always answer me with a question?
On top of that, you're making the act feel so real.
I'm simple-minded, Jinna.
Why do you have to make me feel things?
Gotcha! You're talking to Jinna.
- Huh? - What do you mean?
What? You finished dinner already?
Downed the whole thing.
Don't be shy.
- It's normal. - A grain of rice is on your face.
- Is it? - Yeah.
Wash your mouth first.
No, but you're probably more than just friends, video calling like that.
Are you deaf or something?
- You still haven't finished yours. - Huh?
- Huh? - I'm full already. Hey!
Hey!
You're full of secrets.
- What secrets? I don't have any. - You're lying.
Come to think of it, Anda is quite talented, honey.
I've heard that for the award ceremony, only big-name actors were invited.
Isn't that right, dear?
That's right.
There are several award categories.
Really?
I just want this award to prove that
I'm doing well on the path I've chosen, Dad.
I wonder how prestigious your damn award really is?
Were you defending the country?
In truth, it's just an award for showbiz people.
Worse yet...
they're all cut from the same cloth.
Honey.
When the hell are you going to stop embarrassing me?
Why can't you just be on the right track like Itti, your older brother?
For Itti to rise to such a high rank in the police,
he had to achieve a lot.
That's more like it!
That's what makes it a profession worthy of respect and pride.
So those are the only professions worth being proud of?
Do other professions have no prestige or honor at all?
Am I that worthless for not fighting a criminal?
You're standing here arguing with me nonstop,
and you actually expect me to be proud of your stupid award?
Do you know that you are the problem in this family?
I do!
I also know that you, Dad, never consider me part of it.
You only consider those you deem useful to you. That's it!
Honey!
Anda. Are you hurt? Let me see.
Anda?
I shouldn't have headed home.
I shouldn't have gone to see him.
You went there so you'd know.
So you wouldn't have to wonder about it forever.
He doesn't love me at all.
He never has.
And never will.
Don't worry about those who don't love you.
Those who don't love you, leave them be.
Listen.
I love you the most.
You're the only one I've got left, Kum.
I know.
I won't leave you behind either.
It's okay.
Take a break, everyone. Chop, chop.
Go, go, go.
Oh, so freaking hot.
Jinna.
You've been practicing hard today, so I got you some water.
For me?
Thank you. You didn't have to go to all this trouble.
Trouble? I'm happy to do it.
And are you in a hurry to go home? I want to talk about the scholarship.
Sure thing. I'm not in a hurry.
- Want some? - No, you can have it.
Are you tired from practicing all day?
What's with today?
[Anda: See you tomorrow]
[Jinna: You're not coming today?]
Found you.
What? The coach is calling?
Not him. It's your fans.
They're all waiting to give you snacks like you're a celebrity.
You're bullshitting me.
I know a lot of people have a crush on you,
and I'm surprised that you chose Podduang.
But...
You're serious about my friend, right?
Does it seem like I'm not?
Don't know.
You're half-joking, half-serious.
It's not just me.
I think even Podduang is confused by your personality.
Whatever you're feeling, just say it.
Don't play too many games.
My friend's dense.
If you're not serious, then don't tease him too much.
But if you are, go for it. I'm rooting for you.
How are you getting home, Jinna?
On my motorbike, of course. I do deliveries, so how else?
I thought you'd walk home.
Gosh. Playing soccer is already killing me.
You want a deliveryman to walk home?
- Well, you can just... - That'd be too exhausting.
Podduang.
Take care of this one, too.
And...
It doesn't matter because I've got delivery jobs after this.
Hitting on a girl this late at night,
no wonder you're late for work.
Why do I feel like you're jealous?
I'm not!
I haven't mentioned who it is, so why did you jump the gun?
Or are you really jealous?
Why would I be jealous?
Quit being full of yourself.
Oh?
I've been hitting on you this much, and you're still not giving in?
Stop the act already.
No one's around.
No need to roleplay now.
Why do you always think that what I do for you isn't genuine?
Well. That's just how our deal is.
Is it still necessary, Podduang?
Can we just ignore it?
Just get to the point already.
I'm actually going to hit on you.
No deals, no ulterior motives.
It's just me hitting on you.
Is that okay?
Podduang.
Hey!
Podduang!
What is it?
Why were you so zoned out?
I was just thinking about stuff.
You took hours to clean that plate.
Oh. Don't be ridiculous.
Moving on from the economy, we turn to today's breaking news.
Tragedy strikes as a famous TV actor
- was found dead inside a personal vehicle. - Podduang.
- What is it now? - For the latest updates,
- Come and see this. - we'll go to our reporter
- What news are you talking about? - on the scene.
This is considered today's most shocking event.
A renowned actor who rose to fame in a hit series, Anda,
was found dead inside a private vehicle
at the condo's underground parking lot this early morning.
Preliminarily, authorities speculate that
stress from public criticism may have been a contributing factor
in his taking his own life.
And behind me is the scene where authorities are currently working.
There are police officers and forensic investigators
carefully examining the scene.
This has sent shockwaves through the entertainment industry.
Our deepest condolences go out to the victim's family and the actor's fans.
Anda? The Engineering student?
We will continue to follow this developing story closely
and bring you updates as they come in.
Hey.
That's Anda.
Sir, sir!
Sir!
This is considered today's most shocking event.
A renowned actor who rose to fame in a hit series, Anda,
was found dead inside a private vehicle
at the condo's underground parking lot this early morning.
[No way. #WhatHappenedToAnda] [Breaking! Anda Was Found Dead]
Preliminarily, [Can't believe he took his own life]
authorities speculate that [Who thinks it's a murder case?]
stress from public criticism [The police suspect he died of suffocation]
may have been a contributing factor [Keyboard detectives, stop]
[Anda is gone. Can you stop now?]
in his taking his own life.
And behind me is the scene where authorities
are currently working.
There are police officers and forensic investigators...
Will there be a day when my dad accepts me?
At the end of the day, I feel like I can never truly be myself
as long as I'm still alive.
Jinna.
Do you love me?
Fuck. I do, of course.
Who else am I going to love if not your dumbass?
Dumbass, you say?
At least, I've still got three of my good friends.
Not true at all.
Aside from us, there are so many people who love you too.
Those who love you, they love you for who you are.
At least that includes Kum, right?
I don't know.
I think I should leave.
Thanks a lot for listening to my ramble.
Right.
- Have a safe trip home. - Bye-bye.
Bye.
Fated to die.
Anda!
Get some proper rest if you're sleepy.
Don't sleep in the car.
[Tod: Are you okay?]
[Come to class. Being alone will mess with your head.]
[Come hang out with us.]
Okay. Thank you very much.
Was there no phone, laptop, or tablet belonging to the victim?
We found nothing. We already searched, but found nothing.
Oh, we did find a laptop charger on the car floor.
But it's strange. There was only a charger, not the laptop itself.
A laptop charger.
I think we've got a strange case here.
[Funeral hall: 9]
That's enough. It'll be too heavy to serve.
- This is easy. - How could you let our son die?
It's because you never cared about him.
You never cared about him or accepted who he really was.
It's because of you!
How is this my fault?
I also work and bring money home.
So what? It's just money.
Have you ever brought happiness to our family?
Come on. How is it my fault?
You make money, and what?
- Mom. - Does that make us happy?
- Mom, that's enough. - That's why it ended up like this!
You, too, Itti.
You're a police officer, but you couldn't protect your brother.
That's why he died!
Honey!
Stop blaming it on our son.
Why can't I?
Hey, you...
Mom, take a seat. Please.
Let me do it.
I'll do it. You go and help them there.
You're Anda's close friend, right?
Yes. My name's Jinna.
I'm Itti, his older brother.
Right. I've heard about you.
I must apologize for what happened earlier.
Mom was devastated.
Even now, she still can't accept it.
She lashes out at everyone around her.
I truly have to thank you for staying by Anda's side
while he was still alive,
until the very day he...
It was nothing.
Anda was my best friend.
I never wanted to plan my friend's funeral.
But I'm more than willing to.
If there's anything else about Anda that I can help with, please let me know.
I'll help.
My brother was truly blessed to have you as his friend.
Thank you very much.
What now, Anda?
Jinna.
My shrimp.
It's mine. I claimed it first.
Typical.
- Always fighting each other. - Now, now, Jinna.
Don't throw shade at us, or Podduang might think we're weirdos.
Hey, hey, hey.
Stay still. It'll mess up my shirt.
You're always bitching about stuff, aren't you?
- You're not bitching, right? - What?
Hey, hey, hey! You can't do this. This shirt is a one-off.
Ridiculous, Art.
It's true. See?
I got it from an online thrift store.
You can't get it in this size and print anymore.
It's like destiny.
Aren't you worried they sold you dead people's clothes?
Maybe it was their favorite shirt.
Then their soul might come to haunt you in that shirt.
Come on, that sounds like something out of a horror show.
Everyone wears secondhand clothes.
How about this?
The shrimp you're eating is also dead. Do you know that?
The spirit of that shrimp. Are you scared of it?
Hey. Be careful.
The shrimp spirit.
The shrimp.
- It'll come and get you. - Funny?
Obviously. Tod and Art are funny.
Come and have a meal with us more often.
Come on, we don't have to fight over some shrimp.
We can order some more.
Jinna.
What is it?
Are you crying?
I'm actually fine.
I was riding the motorbike, and the wind made my eyes water.
Really?
Want me to wash your face in my room?
I'm actually not crying, you know?
Right. You're not crying.
Just come with me and wash your face.
Come on. I'll take it off for you.
Come on.
Satang isn't here?
He's away.
He'll be back late. He's been with his friends lately.
What are you looking at?
The one who wasn't crying.
You love teasing people?
My friend's dead.
Let me cry for a bit, okay?
I miss him whenever I'm on the road.
Jinna.
Maybe you don't know it yet, but I really love Anda as an actor.
He's my source of joy.
It broke my heart when someone insulted him.
I was happy when someone complimented him.
And when this happened to him,
I could barely hold myself together.
I just want to tell you that
if you're hurting, just let it out.
Don't worry about how people will see you.
He was your best friend, Jinna.
Everyone understands you.
Can I hug you?
So what is it, Jinna?
It's a murder case, isn't it?
I don't know.
Your guess is as good as mine.
Itti.
Honestly, do you also think this probably wasn't a suicide?
Kum probably has his reasons.
He probably wouldn't hurt Anda.
Leave this to the police.
Don't stick your necks out for anyone.
Amp. Are you all right?
Why...
You must help Anda!
Do you also think that Anda was murdered?
Then how about we both try to uncover the truth?
Let's help Anda.